{
    "id": "7cad64bf87ef471c8ec33e604c1fab90",
    "title": "Question Tags Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "You know everything, …………………………?",
            "description": "A negative tag is after an affirmative sentence. In the simple present tense, use do or does in the question tag.",
            "answers": [
                "do you",
                "don't you",
                "didn't you"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "She helped you, ………………………….?",
            "description": "In the simple past tense, use did in the question tag. ",
            "answers": [
                "did she",
                "didn't she",
                "hadn't she"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "He does hardly anything, …………………………..?",
            "description": "An affirmative tag is used after negative expressions like hardly or nothing. ",
            "answers": [
                "does he",
                "doesn't he",
                "did he"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "She is your sister, ……………………………?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is she",
                "isn't she",
                "wasn't she"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "She bakes cakes, …………………………….?",
            "description": "In the simple present tense, use do or does in the question tag. ",
            "answers": [
                "does she",
                "doesn't she",
                "didn't she"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "You did not do it, …………………………….?",
            "description": "Use an affirmative tag after a negative statement. ",
            "answers": [
                "did you",
                "didn't you",
                "had you"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "He is a good mechanic, …………………………….?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is he",
                "isn't he",
                "doesn't he"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "There is no one in that room, …………………………….?",
            "description": "Use an affirmative tag after negative expressions like no one. ",
            "answers": [
                "is there",
                "isn't there",
                "wasn't there"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "She earns a good salary, …………………………?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "does she",
                "doesn't she",
                "didn't she"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "She refused to go, ……………………………….?",
            "description": "In the simple past tense, use did in the question tag. ",
            "answers": [
                "did she",
                "didn't she",
                "doesn't she"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "You and I saw it, …………………………..?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "did we",
                "didn't we",
                "didn't you and I"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "No one is ready to go, ……………………………?",
            "description": "We use they in question tags after nobody or no one. ",
            "answers": [
                "is anyone",
                "is no one",
                "are they"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        }
    ]
}